

Chaiyong Ragkhitwetsagul ucabagk@ucl.ac.uk Department of Computer Science UCL, London WC1E 6BT

Chaiyong Ragkhiwetsagul

Research Student

www.cs.ucl.ac.uk/staff/C.Ragkhitwetsagul

About me I am currently a 2nd year MPhil/PhD student in Centre for Research on Evolution, Search and Testing (CREST), department of Computer Science at University College London.

I am also an assistant instructor at the Faculty of ICT, Mahidol University who is the main sponsor for my PhD study.

I received a bachelor degree in Computer Engineering from Kasetsart University, Thailand and a master degree in MSIT - Very Large Information Systems (currently called Master of Computational Data Science) from Carnegie Mellon University, PA, USA

Current Projects

Internet-scaled similar code search

A study of similarity of source code in the presence of pervasive modifications

Online source code reuse: a case study of Stackoverflow vs. Qualitas OSS Searching for Configurations in Clone Evaluation

Education

2014 - present, PhD

MPhil/PhD in Computer Science

University College London, UK

Research topic: Large-Scale Source Code Plagiarism Detection

Supervisors: Dr. Jens Krinke, Dr. David Clark

Research interest: clone detection, source code plagiarism detection,

code similarity, mining of software repository

2007 - 2008, Master

MSIT - Very Large Information Systems

Carnegie Mellon University, USA

Capstone project: Honeydew: Predicting meeting date using machine learning algorithm

2002 - 2005, Undergraduate

Bachelor Degree in Computer Engineering (Magna cum Laude)

Kasetsart University, Thailand

Experience

Sep 2014 - Present, Research Student (MPhil/PhD)

Department of Computer Science, University College LondonA member of Centre for Research on Evolution, Search and Testing (CREST) under Software Systems Engineering (SSE) group.

Dec 2012 - Sep 2014, Assistant Instructor

Faculty of ICT, Mahidol University, Nakhonpathom, Thailand

A lecturer of Fundamentals of Programming, OOP, DBMS, Knowledge-based Systems, Android App Development.

A researcher in Mahidol University Electronic Research Information System (MU eRIS) project, and advising 3 undergraduate senior projects.

Nov 2011 - Sep 2014, Consultant

Blaccess Thailand

Making key decisions and providing company's vision.

Planning and managing IT projects and staffs.

Jan 2009 - Nov 2012, System Analyst

National Economic and Social Development Board (NESDB), Thailand

Planning, migrating, and developing new NESDB IT services (email system, web applications, databases, and networks).

IT consultant and network administrator.

Feb 2010 - Dec 2012, Teacher

ProGaming, Thailand

Instructing the Pro Android course focusing on how to develop an Android application.

Instructing the Pro iOS course focusing on how to develop an iOS application.

Jan 2009 - Dec 2012, Research Assistant

Kasetsart University, Thailand

Developing a digital repository, course and training management system, and project tracking system for Puparn Royal Development Study Center.

Mar 2008 - Aug 2008, Intern

Oracle, USA

Developing a new version of testing platform called Distributed Testing System (DTS) using Java Servlet, JSP, and Javascript.

Feb 2006 - Apr 2007, Software Test Engineer

Microsoft, Thailand

Creating automated test tools for testing localized versions of Windows Vista User Assistance Platform.

Testing user assistance (UA) contents in XML format.

Achievements/Awards

2014: Mahidol Universitys Academic Development Scholarship

2014: Faculty of ICT, Mahidol University PhD scholarship

2008: Best Project Award: 15-637 Web App Development, CMU, 2008

2007: The Royal Thai Government scholarship

2006: The winner of the National Software Contest of Thailand (NSC2006)

in Entertainment category

2005: A finalist in DTAC & NOKIA i-Awards mobile app contest

Publications

Ragkhitwetsagul C., Paixao M., Adham M., Busari S., Krinke J., and Drake J.H. (2016). Searching for Configurations in Clone Evalution: A Replication Study. In 8th International Symposium on Search-based Software Engineering (SSBSE): Challenge Track, 2016. North Carolina, USA. *To Appear*

Janviriya, P., Ongarjithichai, T., Numruktrakul, P., Ragkhitwetsagul, C. (2014). CloudyDays: Cloud Storage Integration System. In ICT-ISPC 2014 (pp. 125-128). Nakhonpathom, Thailand.

Hathaiwichian, P., Siriwittayacharoen, L., Wongwachirawanich, A., Ragkhitwetsagul, C. (2014). Android Application for Event Management and Information Propagation. In ICT-ISPC 2014 (pp. 139-142). Nakhonpathom, Thailand.

Skills

Platforms

- Mac
- Linux

- Windows
- Raspberry Pi

Computer programming

- Java
- o C/C++
- Obj-C
- .Net

- HTML
- o PHP
- o SQL

References

References upon request.